CHASE SULLINS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Phone: (615) 519-5989

Email: jcsullins222@yahoo.com

Website:

Linkedin: chasesullins Github: ChaseSully222

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JSON Server
- JavaScript
- React
- React
- Python/Django
- GiHhub

PROJECTS

Front End Capstone: csART

csART is an application that was built for my personal display of spray painting artwork. The application features several login features for its users and a gallery view of the artwork. As the manager of the app, I have the ability to login as the 'admin' of the application. Giving me full CRUD functionality over the Gallery. A user can create an account and login to the app with their credentials. A logged in user has the ability to view the art gallery, and the ability to select their favorite artwork from the Gallery and add that to their 'Favorites' section within the app. Last is a Guest login. This user has the limited ability of only viewing the Gallery, and cannot add any paintings to their favorites section.

- Tech used: React.js , CSS for styling. JSON server to execute API fetch calls

<u>https://github.com/ChaseSully222/Frontend-Capstone</u>

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School.

Full-Time Web Developer Boot-camp, Python/ Django (Jan. - June 2020)

Fleming Training Center

Grade 3 Water Treatment Operator Certification (2015 - 2016)

PERSONAL PROFILE

Creativity and a passion for tech is what drove me to begin a career in software development. Whether its building PC's, writing code, listening to music, browsing the web, or countless hours gaming; I'm always enjoying tech in some capacity. With so many hobbies and interest ingrained in technology, I decided a career in that field was best suited for me. After researching and talking to several friends in the tech field, I found Nashville Software School and dove right in to their intensive 6-month full-stack boot-camp.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Nashville Software School

JR. FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ STUDENT JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

- Six-month, intensive software development bootcamp
- Hands on experience working with teams of developers to build applications using Git and GitHub for version control
- Built individual and team-based projects with full CRUD functionality
- Tech Stack includes HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JSON Server, Reactjs, Python/Django, SQL
- Adapted to the course being moved to a virtual environment, utilizing ZOOM for classroom lessons and group projects.

Southwest Airlines (BNA)

RAMP AGENT

SEPTEMBER 2018 - OCTOBER 2019

- Job positions include Gate Lead, Lead Assist, Baggage/Freight Runners,
- Main position, Gate Lead which is the lead agent in a team of 4 or 5.
- Gate Lead is responsible for the aircraft, baggage, freight, and agents at their assigned gate
- Safely marshal aircraft into the gate and connect ground services.
- Coordinate Loading/Offloading of baggage and freight in a timely manner to ensure ontime departures and baggage pickup.
- Manually or Electronically submit a Cargo Bin Loading Slip to an operations agent. This
 document tracks all commodities loaded onto the aircraft and is critical to the weight and
 balance of the aircraft.

Education Network of America

CUSTOMER SUPPORT ENGINEER

MARCH 2016 - DECEMBER 2017

- Proactively monitor, research, and document WAN issues utilizing network monitoring
 applications (Icinga 2). Report customer facing service impacting issues to the customer
 and actively manage vendors to restore service quickly. Provide direction and guidance to
 vendors to act swiftly and initiate root cause analysis (RCA) to avoid future service impacts.
- Ensure high levels of customer satisfaction by directly resolving or managing all activities to
 restore service. Communicate with customers throughout the incident duration while
 managing the resolution activities. Report all customer communication and
 troubleshooting in a ticketing system (CRM ticketing system) and complete RCA's as
 requested.
- Primary point of contact for customers to call for all services ENA offers. Manage and
 executed changes in firewalls, DNS, and network device configurations to restore service.
 Provides support for Voice over IP (VOIP) including moves/ adds/ changes that may affect
 customer invoices. Affects support and changes to various other technologies: E-mail,
 Content Filtering, DNS.

West Wilson Utility District

WATER TREATMENT PLANT OPERATOR GRADE III MAY 2013- MARCH 2016

- Monitor plant operations and perform corrective action in plant operations while adhering
 to Standard Operating Procedures to ensure finished potable water or discharged water
 quality meets or exceeds the standards of EPA and the Tennessee Department of
 Environment and Conservation.
- Perform all necessary laboratory work required for observation and control of the water treatment plant in order to meet treatment plant, State and Federal regulations.
- Perform maintenance of equipment related to operations of he water treatment plants including calibration of feeders and instruments, repair feeders, pumps, etc.
- Trained to operate Supervisor Control and Data Acquisition (SCADA) system.
- Perform plant calculations for chemical dosages, chemical usage, flow rates, detention time, and all other calculations necessary for the proper operation of the water treatment plant
- Routinely record data of the plants status, tank levels, pump stations and water pressure throughout the water distribution system.